zoffio.com 2015-12-18

# Privacy Policy - Zoffio

Team Zoffio considers personal privacy to be of paramount importance. It governs all its transactions with strict rules thereby ensuring customers with secure transactions that do not violate any privacy policy. As such Team Zoffio uses only customer's name and personal information as directed by the Privacy Policy. We concentrate on collecting information that is relevant to our dealings with you. The collected information is retained with Team Zoffio for as long as required legally and as long as it is relevant for the purposes for which the data was collected. However, it has to be noted that the website allows free surfing and browsing of its content without you having to provide your personal details.

#### Contact Details

Team Zoffio collects customer information to process the order of a product on the site. We use the collected data for further purchase and later claims on the website. The information that we collect includes your name, title, your gender, postal and delivery address, contact number, fax and payment details. Payment details include payment card and bank account details.

#### Uses

We can only accept the placing of your order, process payment for the same and deliver the order to you after you furnish us with your details. It also helps us to keep you updated of the status of your order if we have these details.

We also use your details to manage the website and allow you to use parts of the website which otherwise may be restricted to you. Your personal details also help us to detect fraud or site abuses and credit risk reduction and also to provide you with marketing or customer service assistance. In cases, where we sell the whole or part of the business we may require to transfer our databases that has your personal information.

#### More Uses - Personally Identifiable Information (PII)

Zoffio would like to walk you through the other uses that we may use your information for. First is we may use it for opinion and market research. When we use your information for such purposes we will keep your details anonymous and use it for statistical purposes. 

Zoffio updates its customers by sending information regarding Zoffio, its site, other websites, products, sales promotions, newsletters, and matters relating to Zoffio’s business partners. However you can also unsubscribe from receiving them if you are not eager to receive these updates. Zoffio will process your request within 7 working days.

Zoffio uses personal data to ascertain location and usage of certain aspects of the site. The collected data may be passed on to third parties. The data will be anonymized and as such you will not be identified personally.

We collect personally identifiable information (email address, name, phone number, etc.) from you when you set up a free account. We use your contact information to send you offers based on your previous orders and your interests.

#### Modification/Alteration to Privacy Policy

We may modify, change or alter any part of this privacy policy at any given point of time. The revised privacy policy will be effective immediately after being posted on the Website. Hence, it is the sole responsibility of each & every user to review the privacy policy of the website periodically to know of any revisions made to it.

#### Demographic and Profile Data

Personal information is used to:

Provide the services you request;

To resolve disputes & solve issues.

Understand, measure & analyse consumer interest in the products;

Provide information on product offers & updates;

Promote a genuine service;

Occasionally request participation in online survey.

**Note:** You can send your product to the address stated below:

#### Personal Information:

Personal information may be shared with our other business units to:

Prevent or detect identity theft, fraud and other illegal operations;

Correlate related or multiple accounts to prevent abuse of our services;

We would not rent, trade or share your PII that we have collected with any other company for their marketing purposes without your consent. Though we reserve the right to communicate your personal information to any third party that makes a legally-compliant request for its disclosure. However, we will not disclose your name, address and other information which identifies you personally to any third party without your consent.

Facilitate joint or co-branded services that may be requested by you where such services are provided by more than one business units;

Should such a transaction occur, that other business entity (or the new combined entity) will be required to follow this privacy policy with respect to your personal information

Your IP address will be identified to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our website. Your IP address is also used to help identify you and to gather broad demographic information.

Cookies and other technologies such as pixel tags and clear gifs to store certain types of information each time you visit any page on our website may be used. This enables us to determine what portions of this website are most appropriate for your professional needs and to serve advertising banners to you. You may choose to decline cookies, but this would disable the scope of experiencing the entire features of the website. Hence, we recommend that you leave them turned on.

As we use third-party service providers to serve ads on our behalf across the internet, they may collect anonymous information about your visits to our website, and your interaction with our products and services to target advertisements for goods and services. No personally identifiable information is collected or used in this process.

#### Third Party

However, it has to be noted that there are cases where we require sending across your personal details to the franchisor. It is after your approval that the franchisor can use the information to sell products to you either directly or indirectly to carry out transactions with you. Secondly, we may also send across your details to a third party, for example, courier or delivery agency so they can deliver the product to your address.

It is however to be noted that we do not rent or sell your personal details to anyone nor do we allow anyone to use your details for their marketing interests. We use your personal information in a way that is described by the privacy policy.

Apart from the above mentioned third parties we may also share your details to other companies which are in the same group, agents and sub-contractors primarily to help team Zoffio with the various uses of your details in our data set. We do not encourage the exchange of personal details that do not adhere to the laws of the privacy policy. If we are required to share your personal details to third parties we carry forward with it only after your prior consent. Note that the website may contain links related to third parties or other sites. Zoffio however, is not responsible for any of the privacy policy of these other sites.

We consider the protection of your personal details to be of paramount importance. We therefore take measures to keep your details safe and secure. Your personal details are stored in computers that are protected by physical and technological security devices. We also have third parties that verify our privacy policy. We do not as stated above, sell or rent your personal information to third parties. If we do we communicate your details to only a third party that offers a legally-compliant request for its disclosure.

#### Expectations from You:

Team Zoffio assures the protection of your private details. However, it is expected that as a customer, you should furnish details only that are accurate and keep Team Zoffio updated of any changes that are made.

#### Tracking

You can track the details of your transactions by logging into the website with your details. The details which you can view include the orders that are complete, open and those that are to be dispatched. You are expected to keep your details unavailable to unauthorized third parties. We accept liability of passwords if it is our fault.  
Please furnish your personal details only if you accept the terms and conditions made available here.

#### Fraud Prevention

Team Zoffio takes the required measures to curb any fraudulent activities. Zoffio, therefore has teamed up with standard and authorized agencies that are well endowed with Credit Check and Fraud prevention Policies.

#### Cookies

Cookies as you may be aware are minuscule text files which help Zoffio server to identify your computer as a unique server when you visit pages on our website. Cookies help recognize your internet protocol address.  
You may restrict the use of your cookies. However, this would only affect your usability of your website. You may be banned from visiting certain pages if you do not enable cookies. Zoffio uses cookies only to enhance your experience. Zoffio cookies do not contain personal details and they are free of viruses.  
Cookies are used to recognize the internet browser. The data that are collected are not used without separate authorization of the user to identify visitors to Zoffio website; neither is it collated with personal data on the created pseudonym holder.

#### Security

Zoffio transactions are secured by technologies like firewall and Secure Socket Layer Coding (SSL). All the transactions are held by secure servers. To keep your transactions secure you should be careful about sending your details in unencrypted electronic communications with Zoffio. We may as a measure to secure your financial details and transactions require you to provide proof of identity before disclosing information to you. You are completely responsible to keep your password secure and safe from unrequired access.

#### Copyright

Zoffio has complete copyright over the Privacy Policy discussed. Violation of the copyright is not allowed by any party. The violation of Zoffio copyright will be subject to legal action.
